Finding Aid for the The Andrew Nelson Lytle Addition
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Incoming Correspondence: Brush, B. - Bryant, J. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Bryant, J. - Buffington, R. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Bunnenberg, M. - Burns, G. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Burton, L. - Campbell, M. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Campbell, P. - Campbell, T. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Campbell, T. - Cannon, T. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Cantrill, J. - Carvey, H. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: [Carws, E.] - Cash, J. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Cater, I. - Cheatham, D. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Cheek, L. - Cheney, F. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Cheuse, A. - Childers, B. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Childress, M. (1 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Childress, M. (2 of 2) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Chitty - Clark, B. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Clark, C. - Clemet, F. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Cleveland, F. - Coleman, R. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Coles, N. - Condon, D. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Condon, D. - Conway, S. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Cooney, M. - Core, G. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Core, G. - Cornett, A. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Cornett, N. - Cowley, M. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Cowley, M. - Crews, H. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Crews, H. - Crimmins, S. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Crocker, H. - Cutrer, T. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Dalrymple, A. - Davenport, J. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Davis, A. - Davis, D. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Day, R. (1 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Day, R. (2 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Day, R. (3 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Day, R. (4 of 4) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Day, R. - Deaver, S. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Deaver, S. - Dennis, T. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Dennis, T. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Dennis, T. - Dickson, E. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Dickson, E. - Divine, R. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Divine, R. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Dodson, P. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Dodson, P. - Driver (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Duckworth, W. - Dupree, T. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Dupree, T. - Elder, K. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Engsbery, P. - England, P. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Erwin, P. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Eschbach, N. - Evans, D. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Fain, J. - Farrell, M. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Ferguson, K. - Fitzgerald, N. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Fitzgerald, R. - Foata, A. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Foata, A. (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Foata, A. (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Foata, A. (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Foata, A. - Ford, J. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Fort, K. - Frazer, W. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (1 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (2 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (3 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (4 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (5 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (6 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (7 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (8 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (9 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (10 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (11 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (12 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Frederiksen, A. (13 of 13) (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Freeman, D. - Garrett, G. (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Garrett, G. - Gerber, M. (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Gerber, M. (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Gerber, M. - Gilfry, W. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Gilfry, W. - Graham, A. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Graham, E. - Graves, J. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Graves, J. - Green, F. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Green, F. (1 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Green, F. (2 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Green, F. (3 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Green, R. - Greene, E. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Greene, E. - Griffin, C. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Griffin, W. - Griffith, O. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Griffith, O. - Grogan, K. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Gulledge, J. - Hall, S. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hallman, D. (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hallman, D. (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hallman, D. - Hansell, P. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hansen, K. - Hassler, A. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Haun, R. - Hay, J. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hay, J. - Heck, S. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Heck, S. (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Heck, S. (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Heck, S. - Heflin, F. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Heilman, R. - Henenburg, R. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Herndon, J. - Hess, L. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hetrick, L. - Hiers, L. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: High, D. - Hill, J. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hines, S. - Hitt, J. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hitt, J. - Hogan, W. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Holladay, R. - Hornsby, S. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Hornsby, S. - Howell, S. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Howell, S. - Howorth, S. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Howorth, S. - Hutson, R. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Igarashi, P. - Jackson, L. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Jackson, J. - Jarrett, B. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Jarrett, B. - Jenrette, R. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Jetmundsen, N. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Jetmundsen, N. - Johnston, F. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Johnston, T. - Juhan, F. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Kaser, D. - Keeble, A. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: [Kiab], D. - Kilgo, J. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Kilgo, J. - Kirk, R. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Kirk, R. - Kirkpatrick, S. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Kizima, M. - Koch, C. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Koch, C. (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Koch, C. (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Koch, C. - Kohn, S. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Kohn, S. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Kramer, V. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Kramer, V. - Landess, T. (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Landess, T. (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Landess, T. - Law, P. (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Law, P. (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Law, P. (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Lawrence, S. - Leach, E. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Leatherman, L. - Leslie, W. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Leonard, J. - Little, L. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Little, L. - Lorentz, P. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Lorentz, P. - Lowell, R. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Lowes, M. - Lucas, M. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Lucas, M. - Lulton, C. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Lyman, G. - Lytle, C. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Lytle - Lytle, E. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Lytle, G. - Lytle, H. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Lytle, H. - Lytle, R. (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: MacDonald, M. - MacInnes, M. (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Madden, D. - Makowsky, V. (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Makowsky, V. - Manfred, F. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Manfred, F. - Mather, R. (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Mather, R. - Mathis, B. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Mathis, B. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: May, P. - McCrady, T. (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: McCuen, W. - McDowell, D. (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: McIlhenny, P. - McMillan, D. (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: McMillan, D. (1 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: McMillan, D. (2 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: McMillan, D. (3 of 3) (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: McNabb, E. - Menendez, D. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Meriwether, J. - Middleton, D (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Middleton, D. - Middleton, F. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Middleton, F. (1 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Middleton, F. (2 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Middleton, F. (3 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Mignery, A. - Mitchell, R. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Mitchell, R. - Montague, R. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Montgomery, M. - Moore, H. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Moore, M. - Murrah, J (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Nagel, E. - Nardin, F. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Nelson, A. - New, M. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Nicaud, R. - Nicholson, J. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Nielson, C. - Nimocks, M. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Nims, J. - Odom, J. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Odom, J. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Odom, J. - Owen, J. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Owens, E. - Owsley, H. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Paden, C. (1 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Paden, C. (2 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Paden, C. (3 of 3) (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Paden, C. - Page, O. (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Page, O. - Parker, R. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Parker, R. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Parker, T. - Parra, A. (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Parsley, H. - Paschall, R. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Patterson, G. - Person, J. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Person, J. - Pintle, A. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Pittard, M. - Plater, R. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Poe, G. - Porter, J. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Porter, K. - Potter, H. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Potter, H. - Powell, L. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Powell, M. - Provost, E. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Prunty, W. - Purifoy, T. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Quinby, G. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Quinby, G. - Ralston, W. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Ralston, W. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Ralston, W. - Ransom, J. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Raoul, W. - Reddick, A. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Reeves, J. - Richards, [S.] (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Richards, S. (1 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Richards, S. (2 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Richards, S. (3 of 3) (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Richardson, D. - Riis, E. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Riis, E. - Robinson, J. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Robinson, J. - Rochford, J. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Rock, V. - Rogers, C. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Roland, C. - Ross, J. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Ross, J. - Rubin, L. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Rubin, L. - Ryan, S. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Salamon, L. - Sanders, J. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Sanders, J. - Sanders, R. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Sarcone, E. - Saussy, H. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Saussy, H. (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Saussy, H. (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Savoy, N. - Scarritt, T. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Scarritt, T. - Scott, W. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Scott, W. - Sheller, J. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Sheller, J. - Shenandoah (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Sherman, L. - Shofner, W. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Shofner, W. - Simpson, C. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Simpson, L. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Sims, A. - Smith, B. (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Smith, S. - Smith, W. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Smith, W. - Spaar, L. (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Spaar, L. - Stafford, C. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Stanely, S. - Stang, S. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Starr, W. - Statham, R. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Steele, J. - Stevenson, J. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Stevenson, J. - Stillman, C. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Stirling, T. - Strange, B. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Strange, B. - Sullivan, J. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Sullivan, J. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Sullivan, J. - Sullivan, M. (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Sullivan, W. - Swetman, G. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Taggart - Tate, C. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Tate, C. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Tate, J. - Tate, S. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Taylor, E. - Taylor, M. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Taylor, M. - Tennet, J. (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Tennet, J. - Thompson, A. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Thompson, J. - Tillinghast, R. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Tillinghast, R. - Tucker, D. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Turlington, B. - Upshaw, P. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Usrey, K. - Vann, K. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Van Winkle, J. - Wagner, T. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Waite, J. - Waldrop, F. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Walker - Ward, T. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Ward, T. - Warren, R. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Warren, R. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Warren, R. - Watson, L. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Weatherby, H.L. - Wentworth, R. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Incoming Correspondence: West, J. - Weston, R. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Weyman, B. (1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Weyman, B. (2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wheelock, J. - Williams, R. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Williamson, C. - Wilson, B. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wilson, C. (1 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wilson, C. (2 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wilson, C. (3 of 3) (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wilson, J. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wilson, J. - Wilson, M. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wilson, R. - Wise, A. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Withers, C. - Wolfe, G. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wolfe, G. - Wolfe, M. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wood, A.T. - Wright, S. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Wright, S. - Yarbrough, T. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Yarbrough, T. - York, L. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Young, D. - Zimmer, P. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Unidentified (1 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Unidentified (2 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Unidentified (3 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Unidentified (4 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Unidentified (5 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Unidentified (6 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Incoming Correspondence: Unidentified (7 of 7) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Personal Correspondence: Lytle, Edna (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Personal Correspondence: Lytle, Kate (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Personal Correspondence: Lytle, Langdon (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Personal Correspondence: Lytle, Lillie Bell (Andrew's Mother) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Personal Correspondence: Past Girlfriends (1922-1936) (1 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Personal Correspondence: Past Girlfriends (1922-1934) (2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence: Patton, Sarah L. (Aug. 1929 - Nov. 10, 1931) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence: Patton, Sarah L. (Nov. 21, 1931 - Dec. 30, 1931) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Personal Correspondence: Patton, Sarah L. (Jan. 3, 1932 - Feb. 14, 1932) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Personal Correspondence: Patton, Sarah L. (Feb. 25, 1932 - Apr. 2, 1932) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Personal Correspondence: Patton, Sarah L. (Apr. 25, 1932 - Jun. 20, 1932) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Personal Correspondence: Patton, Sarah L. (July 4, 1932 - Aug. 27, 1932) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Personal Correspondence: Patton, Sarah L. (Aug. 29, 1932 - Sept. 23, 1944) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Personal Correspondence: Lytle, Robert (Andrew's Father) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Family Correspondence: (1 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Family Correspondence: (2 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Family Correspondence: (3 of 3) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Not to or from Lytle (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Postcard Collection (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Series II. Writings
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (1 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (2 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (3 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (4 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (5 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (6 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (7 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (8 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (9 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (10 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Writings - Collections: From Eden to Babylon (11 of 11) (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Writings - Essays: Afterword, A Semi-Centennial (1 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Essays: Afterword, A Semi-Centennial (2 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Essays: Afterword, A Semi-Centennial (3 of 3) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Essays: Agrarians Today (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Essays: Backwoods Progression (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Essays: Bedford Forrest and His Critter Company (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Essays: Can You Teach Creative Writing (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Writings - Essays: Christian University and the Word (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Writings - Essays: Christian University and the Word (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Writings - Essays: Concerning Warren's All The King's Men (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Writings - Essays: Forest of the South (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Writings - Essays: Forward for Selected Essays of Frank Lawrence Owsley (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Writings - Essays: Hero and the Doctrinaires of Defeat (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Writings - Essays: Hero with the Private Parts (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Writings - Essays: Hind Tit (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Writings - Essays: How Many Miles to Babylon (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Writings - Essays: Jericho, Jericho, Jericho (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Writings - Essays: John Taylor and the Political Economy of Agriculture (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Writings - Essays: Journey South (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (1 of 5) (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (2 of 5) (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (3 of 5) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (4 of 5) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (5 of 5) (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (1 of 8) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (2 of 8) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (3 of 8) (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (4 of 8) (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (5 of 8) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (6 of 8) (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (7 of 8) (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Writings - Essays: Kristin (8 of 8) (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Writings - Essays: Lincoln Myth (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Writings - Essays: Mahogany Frame (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Writings - Essays: Mirror, Mirror, on the Wall (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Writings - Essays: Momentary Man (1 of 5) (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Writings - Essays: Momentary Man (2 of 5) (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Writings - Essays: Momentary Man (3 of 5) (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Writings - Essays: Momentary Man (4 of 5) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Writings - Essays: Momentary Man (5 of 5) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Writings - Essays: Myth In A Garden (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Writings - Essays: Order of Grownmen (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Writings - Essays: Principles of Secession (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Writings - Essays: Search for Order in the American Society (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Writings - Essays: Small Farm Secures the State (Box 17, Folder 7)